https://www.digitalilluminationinterface.org/privacy-policy.html

Our websites use cookies on your device to give you the best user experience. By using our websites, you agree to the placement of these cookies. To learn more, read our privacy policy.
AboutAbout DiiATrademarks & LogosFAQsBoard Members & StaffLiaisonsPresentations & DownloadsDALIIntroducing DALIDALI key features & dimmingDALI-2 versus DALI version-1Systems and product typesDALI & WirelessDALI & IPStandardsIEC 62386 StandardDiiA SpecificationsDALI DataDALI-2 Colour ControlDALI-2 SensorsDALI EmergencyDALI-2 certificationOverview of DALI-2 CertificationStatus of DALI-2 CertificationTimelineD4iD4i OverviewD4i CertificationZhaga-D4iProductsProduct DatabaseProduct ShowcaseTesting & Test HousesDALI-2 LuminairesDALI Version-1 ProductsMembersOur MembersBenefits by CategoryHow to Join DiiADALI for luminaire makersNews & EventsDALI Lighting AwardsLatest DiiA NewsProjects & Case StudiesArticlesMember News & Press CoverageNewsletter & Mailing ListEventsDALI China Summit 2021
LoginContact
Home
Privacy policy
At Digital Illumination Interface Alliance, we respect your privacy. We want to ensure that you get the information, content, and experiences that matter most to you. DiiA, a member of ISTO federation of member alliance programs is committed to protecting the privacy of its members, customers, volunteers, and other contacts. It is the policy of ISTO to not request, collect, or maintain personal data other than what is required for the reasonable and necessary conduct of its trade associations.
Please find the full privacy policy here.
© 2020 Digital Illumination Interface Alliance. All rights reserved. DALI,
the DALI Logo, DALI-2, the DALI-2 Logo, DiiA, the DiiA Logo, D4i and the D4i
Logo are trademarks in various countries in the exclusive use of the Digital
Illumination Interface Alliance.
Privacy policy
Terms of use
Contact
